Yes, I am Yuna Nakamura, a reporter of Mezomemasu Nighttime Entertainment Corner.
Today, I would like to interview Ms. Sakurayama, who is scheduled to appear in Yoruen Land vol. 4.
Okay, let's go.
Ah, I found it. Please introduce yourself.
Yes.
It's a long way, a very long way.
I'm Sakurayama, attendance number 16, from Ehime City Private Junior High School. I look forward to meeting you.
You have a very nice smile.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Sakurai, I understand that you are scheduled to appear in "Night Land vol. 4" on December 5,
How do you feel now?
Well, I am nervous because it will be my first time on stage,
I'm nervous because it's my first time to perform on stage, but it's going to be a very interesting and varied stage called "Kondo Isamu Akira,
I hope everyone will come and see it,
I hope you will all come and see it.
We are rehearsing hard.
Yes, thank you very much.
You play the role of Yusho this time, Mr. Sakurai, and your name suits you very well.
Yes, I get a lot of compliments on it. They say that "Yuuaki" suits you very well,
I leave it to you to decide whether it is good or bad.
Of course they mean it in a good way. Thank you very much.
So, today, I would like to interview you about various things,
First of all, let's see....
What is your favorite food?
My favorite food is bread and ice cream.
Oh, great machine.
Bread and ice cream.
Yes, that's right. Whenever I go to the bread corner, I spend 10 minutes agonizing over the bread, and after looking at it, I end up leaving without buying it.
Yes.
Yes. Yes, I do.
Mr. Sakurai, I often hear you say that you like bread.
Melon bread. Yes, that's right.
Ah, yes. Melon bread. Yes, that's right.
Yes, it is. I often see people eating them. Yes, I do.
Emma Sakurai, you are very fashionable in your personal clothes, and I understand that you like passion.
Oh, yes, I do.
When I put together a passion, I try to put in only three colors, and I also try to use small accessories. Clothes are simple, but I try to be fashionable with lots of accessories, such as catsuits and rings.
I see. Yes, I do. Yes, that's right.
I think we have learned a lot about you, Ms. Sakurayama,
Then, I would like to ask you one last question,
What kind of person is Yuna Nakamura from your point of view?
Are you Yuna Nakamura? Yes, I am.
Yes, I am. She has a small face, she is very small in height, and she has big eyes,
She has big eyes and is very cute,
But the Ebichu family members are aware of it,
I'm sure some of you may have noticed something about her,
But, I think some of the Ebichu family members may have noticed something. What's going on? I think some of you may have noticed it, but sometimes she acts in a way that makes you wonder, "What's wrong with her?
Anyway, Rina Nakamura is very good at singing songs.
When she learns the choreography for the songs of EBITCHU, she makes up her own dubbed songs,
She is so good at it that I would like to see her perform it at some point.
She is an interesting girl.
I'll practice it some more.
I'll practice it some more. By all means. She is so good that I would like to see her perform in various places,
Please practice.
I was so surprised when you said that,
I was so surprised that my heart almost stopped.
I thought, "Oh my God, they are going to make me do this now,
I thought, "What am I going to do, I can't think of anything,
But he was very kind and said I could practice afterwards,He was very kind and said I could practice afterwards,
Next time I meet with Mr. Yoma,
I think I will talk to Mr. Nighttime, and I will talk to Mr. Nighttime.
Yes, I will.
So, Mr. Sakurayama, you will appear in Yoruen Land Vol. 4.
Mr. Sakurayama will appear in Yoruen Land Vol. 4, and that is Mr. Sakurayama,
You know, you are very, very, very, very, very cute at the end,
I would like you to end with a very, very, very, very cute word.
Please do!
Yes, uh..,
Nighttime, hmm?
I'll definitely be waiting for you at Nighttime Land.
Yay! Thank you!
It's not fair to end with "yay". You should have ended it with a "yay".
Really?
I'll definitely be waiting for you at Night Land!
Yes, it was cute. That's what I'm talking about. Yes, well, thank you very much, Mr. Sakurayama. Thank you very much.